KHAOULA **JABOUR**

2600 Golden Horseshoe circle Apt H, Morrisville, NC, 27560 | 919-717-9368

Khaoulajabour4@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/khaoula-jabour-177b5214b/ |

https://khaoulaja.github.io/react-portfolio/

A motivated and highly skilled Computer Science and Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp graduate with 2 years of experience, including operations support and multiple internships. Proven knowledge of database design and creation, programming, web development, and IT support. An aspiring professional with good communication skills and a strong desire to learn in a teamwork environment.

EXPERIENCE

MAR 2019 - JAN 2020

OPERATIONS SUPPORT, FEDASO/EXELA TECHNOLOGIES – FES, MOROCCO

- Respond to incoming tickets on behalf of clients, using Redmine as a ticketing system, to provide the accurate and appropriate information
- Facilitate order management process order intake, input into internal systems
- Respond to user support requests, identify client issues, and correct problems using given methods
- Resolve issues discovered during checkups
- · Develop new innovative solutions to improve the productivity of the technical support personnel
- Document patches and procedural changes for future reference

DEC 2018 - FEB 2019

INTERN, QUINTEL SARL – TANGER, MOROCCO

- Design and create a job search website using Laravel, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap... etc.
- Edit some existing websites
- Create static websites with WordPress

SEP 2017- DEC 2017

FREELANCE, LA ROCHELLE DE FRANCE – KHENIFRA, MOROCCO

- Design and implement a payment management application for the center to process students' payments using JavaFX
- Install new hardware such as new PCs and Printers

JUL 2017

INTERN, THE URBAN MUNICIPALITY – M'DIQ, MOROCCO

- Install, test, upgrade and configure workstations, peripheral equipment, and software as assigned
- Utilize troubleshooting techniques to resolve hardware, software, and network issues
- Perform other duties as directed by Supervisor
- Edit/input, scan, convert and format documents

EDUCATION

NOV 2021 - MAR 2022

CODING BOOTCAMP, UNC CHAPEL HILL

Full-stack web development

JUL 2017

BACHELOR'S DEGREE, SUPERIOR SCHOOL OF TECHNOLOGIE - MEKNES, MOROCCO

Development of information and communication systems (Software development)

JUL 2016

ASSOCIATED DEGREE, SUPERIOR SCHOOL OF TECHNOLOGIE – MEKNES, MOROCCO

Computer Science

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, React, Git, Responsive Web Design, Bootstrap, Foundation, JAVA Script, jQuery, Web APIs, Node.js, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Express, SQL, Object-Relational Mapping (ORM), MVC, MongoDB, WordPress, PhpMyAdmin, SQL Server, FileZilla, Linux/Unix, Microsoft office (word, excel, PowerPoint), Arduino. Languages: English, French, Arabic.